- Hello, Stuart.
- Hey, Sheldon.
(Stuart:)- Help you with anything?
- Yes.
(Sheldon:)I'm attending a party this weekend
for a 93-year-old woman.
(Sheldon:)Can you recommend a gift?
(Stuart:)Uh, I don't know.
(Stuart:)Could put a tennis ball on the end
of Excalibur...
(Stuart:)...make a pretty bad-ass cane.
Do you supply the ball?
(Sheldon:)- No.
- Then no.
(Sheldon:)- What else?
- Uh, oh.
Got this collector's edition
Batman Utility BeIt.
Maybe she could use it
as a wearable pill caddy.
(Sheldon:)Well, she'd just look silly wearing that
without the rest of the costume.
Um, sorry, Sheldon, that's it.
That's all I got.
It's not your fauIt.
l've been to the model-train store.
l've been to Radio Shack.
This woman's impossible to shop for.
l'd make fun of Sheldon
for having girl problems...